{
  "preserveQuestionOrder": false,
  "preserveRoundOrder": false,
  "author": "mrs_royal_flush",
  "questions": [
    {
      "category": "'OK, but what's your REAL name?'",
      "question": "'My name is Farrokh Bulsara and I'm the lead singer of...'",
      "correct": "Queen",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Electric Light Orchestra",
        "Cheap Trick",
        "Bad Company"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'OK, but what's your REAL name?'",
      "question": "'Lady Madonna, what did your mamma name ya?'",
      "correct": "Madonna",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Michelle",
        "Mary",
        "Magdalena"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'OK, but what's your REAL name?'",
      "question": "'My father is Stephen King; of course I have a pen name!'",
      "correct": "Joe Hill",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Robert Kirkman",
        "Scott Thomas",
        "Kelly Braffet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'OK, but what's your REAL name?'",
      "question": "'Hi, I'm Norma Jeane Mortenson.'",
      "correct": "Marilyn Monroe",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Mamie Van Doren",
        "Audrey Hepburn",
        "Jayne Mansfield"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'OK, but what's your REAL name?'",
      "question": "'I am Vin Diesel.'",
      "correct": "Mark Sinclair",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "James Androids",
        "Harry Shields",
        "Vincent Davies"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'Sure, I game...'",
      "question": "Which of these is NOT traditionally played on a chequered board?",
      "correct": "Backgammon",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Chess",
        "Draughts",
        "Amazons"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'Sure, I game...'",
      "question": "Which Pac-Man ghost is described correctly?",
      "correct": "Red Blinky",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Orange Inky",
        "Blue Pinky",
        "Pink Clyde"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'Sure, I game...'",
      "question": "'It's only a game so put up a real good fight...' is the opening line of which game show?",
      "correct": "Big Break",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Blankety Blank",
        "Wipeout",
        "The Moment of Truth"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'Sure, I game...'",
      "question": "Which of these countries hosted the summer Olympic games most recently?",
      "correct": "China",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Greece",
        "Australia",
        "Spain"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "'Sure, I game...'",
      "question": "'A Game of Shadows' was the sequel to which 2009 film?",
      "correct": "Sherlock Holmes",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Paranormal Activity",
        "Valkyrie",
        "Invictus"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Composers from Pieces",
      "question": "Für Elise",
      "correct": "L.V. Beethoven",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "W.A. Mozart",
        "J. Haydn",
        "J.C. Bach"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Composers from Pieces",
      "question": "Erlkönig",
      "correct": "F. Schubert",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "R. Schumann",
        "C.P.E. Bach",
        "G. Mahler"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Composers from Pieces",
      "question": "Messiah",
      "correct": "G.F. Handel",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "J.S. Bach",
        "T. Tallis",
        "F. Couperin"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Composers from Pieces",
      "question": "Danse Macabre",
      "correct": "C. Saint-Saëns",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "D. Shostakovich",
        "W.F. Bach",
        "M. Mussorgsky"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Composers from Pieces",
      "question": "The Love for Three Oranges",
      "correct": "S. Prokofiev",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "S. Rachmaninov",
        "P.I. Tchaikovsky",
        "N. Rimsky-Korsakov"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pre-flight Panic",
      "question": "KEF",
      "correct": "Iceland",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Spain",
        "Norway",
        "Italy"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pre-flight Panic",
      "question": "STN",
      "correct": "London",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Southampton",
        "Birmingham",
        "Manchester"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pre-flight Panic",
      "question": "LHR to SYD",
      "correct": "UK to Australia",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "France to China",
        "India to USA",
        "Brazil to South Africa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pre-flight Panic",
      "question": "FRA",
      "correct": "Frankfurt",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Fresno",
        "Faridabad",
        "Foshan"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Pre-flight Panic",
      "question": "JFK",
      "correct": "New York",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "California",
        "Florida",
        "Texas"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Michelangelo, Raphael, Donatello and Caravaggio are all what?",
      "correct": "Artists",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles",
        "Chefs",
        "Architects"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "'I'm George Orwell and I certainly did NOT write...'",
      "correct": "The Sun Also Rises",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Animal Farm",
        "Nineteen Eighty-Four",
        "Keep the Aspidistra Flying"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Which of these is NOT a plant?",
      "correct": "Peruvian Inca Orchid",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Blue Tango Bromeliad",
        "Tibetan Poppy",
        "Canada Lily"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Who wrote 'The Odyssey'?",
      "correct": "Homer",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Plato",
        "Sophocles",
        "Herodotus"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "General Knowledge",
      "question": "Edward the Black Prince was the father of which English king?",
      "correct": "Richard II",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Henry I",
        "John",
        "Edward III"
      ]
    }
  ]
}